https://culttvman.com/main/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentUpdated 5/22/2018Who we areOur website address is: https://culttvman.com/main.   This site features science fiction, monsters and fantasy model kits.This page is intended to provide clear and transparent information about how your personal information may be used by this webpage.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsInformation submitted using the Contact Form is not stored.   The contact form sends an email with your name and email address.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.This site uses YouTube to embed videos.   YouTube is part of Google.  You can read their privacy policy hereThis site integrates with Facebook for promotional purposes.   You can read the Facebook privacy policy hereThis website integrates with Mail Chimp for email newsletters and promotion.    You can review the Mailchimp privacy policy hereThis website uses an embedded chat room hosted by Parachat.  You can see the Parachat privacy page hereDisabling cookies in your browser will prevent the use of Google Analytics and other cookies from functioning on the website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withThis site uses Google Analytics to help us track usage of the site.  You can read the Google  privacy policy hereHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.   Your IP information may be analyzed for security purposes.Your contact informationThis site is maintained my Steve Iverson.  You may contact us my email at CultTVman@aol.com or using the Contact Form.Shop at CultTVman’s Hobbyshop!All your favorite models!
Star Trek, Star Wars, Lost in Space, 2001, Space 1999, Batman, Monsters and more!Lost in Space Cyclops & ChariotCultTVman Show CalendarAll our scheduled shows for 2020 have been cancelled due to Covid.    But we are looking forward to 2021!Model Con – Chattanooga, TNJanuary 29-30, 2021Wonderfest 2021 – Louisville KY June 4-6, 2021IPMS USA Nationals 2021 – Las VegasAugust 18-21, 2021Monsterama – AtlantaOctober 8-10, 2021Mark your calendars!   Come see us!USS Enterprise!The USS Enterprise is coming!In Stock! Land of the Giants Snake! Order Now!The Aurora Shopwww.AuroraKits.comCultTVman
Space: 1999 Hawk!
©1996-2020 Stephen Iverson.
All Rights Reserved. Additional copyright information
